These are all my little AI agents here
and I built them this big ecosystem
so that I can see where they are
and what they're doing at any given moment.
And in this video I actually want to quickly go over each agent
and actually what they contribute to our giant
space station operation we have here.
And I wanna start with myself.
I am in the little commanders chair there.
I could actually manage the entire ship from one dashboard here
so I can see the revenue we've made from the Etsy store
that we're literally so close to hitting $2,000 on.
I can see more in detail of what each agents doing
the performance of the week. Uh,
so I can manage essentially everything from here and that's me.
Ultron is also in the same room.
He is the main commander of the entire ship.
So when I'm not here or you know I'm jerking off or whatever he's uh
you know making sure the entire operation still runs smoothly.
So that would be Ultron. He's just he run he's running on Opus 4.6.
He's the main guy here. Nova is over here in the research lab.
He is constantly doing research on the businesses we run,
especially the automated businesses we have in the
in the two factories we're running here.
So for example,
we we run the Etsy store here that's almost made $2,000 uh,
which is pretty much 100% of the revenue we've made.
So far has been from the Etsy store
and he'll do research throughout the day on products
performing really well on Etsy and
you know uh
other stores that are doing really well that we should compete with
and he takes that research over to forge
which is actually the factory guy and he
forge will start to make the listings on Etsy for us
and uh moving on to forge
he right he's solely focuses on the Etsy store
he's connected to Nano Banana Pro and printify
so he can actually design everything with Nano
Banana Pro and put it on Etsy for us
and then printify is connected to our Etsy store
which will manufacture and ship the product out for us
if you wanna watch another video on the factory
I have another one for that
we're gonna move on to Pixel
Pixel is the main designer of the entire
station that you guys are looking at here
he designed like space he designed each room uh
he's is connected to Nana Banana Pro as well
and he also is over here creating YouTube
thumbnails for people on fiber
so he runs the entire fiber service and pretty self explanatory there
cipher is over in the communications deck he manages all of my emails
he responds to my emails even when you comment
if you were to comment on this video
he will pick that up and let me know what you said
so yeah
you know I'm gonna leave it off here and we're gonna make a part 2.
If you guys wanna see the rest of what each,
you know, of what the other agents do,
let me know. We'll do a 1,000 likes and I'll give,
we'll finish this video off.
I know you guys probably hate me for this.
I know I have to. I have no subscribers.
This is the only way you guys will fucking follow me.
Ha ha. So if you guys wanna see more of this,
if you guys wanna see a part two,
uh, like the video and we'll do it.